are you a nerd 100% and here's have here
to help us learn more is professional
nerd watcher King Vader would you like
any water coffee refreshments water
would be great
[Music]
so weapons it's mostly led a nerd is
defined as a person who would look up
the word nerd in the dictionary and you
know you're not a nerd because you're
incredibly fit you're the king of
muscles and you're about to compete in
your gyms weightlifting competition to
get pumped up you take anabolic steroids
usually have a little as a treat but
this is a competition so you double your
gym candy dosage you feel stronger than
ever before you pull the barbell up to
your chest but just as you stash the 200
pounds over your head you see a
commercial on the gyms TVs you see it's
a story of a mother presenting a bowl of
hot soup to her son this reminds you of
when you were in second grade and kids
would make fun of you because your mom
would always pack hot soup for lunch
even on a sweltering June day you'd be
the kid drinking Rocklin Chatterley out
of a thermos normally you'd be able to
brush his memory aside but you're so
hopped up on roids that the hormones are
completely out of whack you begin to sob
uncontrollably and drop your wings
everyone the audience thinks your
blubbering because the competition is
too hard and between snot fields sobs
you try to explain no it's my mommy
which only makes it worse the gym takes
your photo off there muscle man wall it
puts it in the nerds not wanted section
let's say nothing makes you cry except
onions everyone cries with her onions
around they're so mean but you're a
tough guy because you grew up with a
military dad he used to say son
every time you shut a tear a soldier
goes AWOL you spend your childhood
moving from army base to army base at 18
you enlist by the time you're 30 you
lived in all 50 states eating every kind
of hotdog seen every kind of bird so
when you and your GI pals find yourself
at a bar on trivia night you decide okay
play the winner gets free beer and
liking beer is a classic non nerd
behavior the final round is to write
down all the state flowers you imagine
all the brewskis you'll be pass it to
your bros and fill out the answer sheet
in seconds you're so focused on winning
you don't realize knowing all the state
flowers is classic their behavior but
the talents go in the audience does
she's been scouting Bar trivia nights
for months on the hunt to find the
perfect nerd for the win Ben Stein's
money reboot and a meathead who doesn't
realize he's a nerd is the shooter sing
wow she's been after when she hands you
the contract you think it's just a
waiver to get your free suds you have no
idea you've just agreed to be the new
face of win this nerds money as soon as
the military gets wind of your casting
you're dishonorably discharged even as a
civilian you can't enter a bar without
everyone shouting nerd and they'll be
right let's say you never pursue trivia
the only fact you know is how to have a
good time you're a cool dude who's
always invited to parties and just now a
friend that called you up and invite you
to a party at his friend's house or at
least that's what you think you heard
you took the call while riding your big
bad motorcycle and you just upgrade the
muffler so your bike sounds bigger and
better but your hogs powerful pipes make
it hard to hear anything else so when
your friend says when they go to my
friend's circus themed party you'd think
he says when they go to an Andy Serkis
themed party you show up in a golem
costume makes sense
it's Andy circuses best role when
everyone stares you assume it's because
they're blown away by your attention to
detail to get further into character you
creep up to the hosts whisper hi
precious
as you steal the ring right off her
finger she tries to snatch it back but
you're so low to the ground she instead
rips off your loincloth underwear and
exposes your teeny tiny penis which has
shrunk significantly due to the
prolonged pressure on your perineum
thanks to the vibrations from your
motorcycles powerful engine 100 percent
confirmed everyone laughs and points
that your little loser Willie you're
never getting invited to another party
again unless it's one of those mean
parties where the cool people compete to
bring the biggest nerd let's say you're
never socially awkward everyone laughs
at your jokes because you wanted the
richest men in America you creosote
should be a platform that now rules the
world sure the reason you made it was
because she was too nervous to talk to
girls and instead rated them as hot or
not from the safety of your own dorm
room but now that's in the past now
you're the father of a website that
connects France and destroys democracies
everyone boughs at your feet no one even
makes fun of your Caesar haircut until
you're requested to defend yourself in
front of Congress still shouldn't be a
problem
you've hired the best consultants money
can buy they tell you to bring a booster
seat so you look more intimidating in
the photo so you buy the most expensive
tallest one it should be something no
one notices over you're now imposing
frame but instead everyone can't stop
talking about Mark Zuckerberg spud
pillow your photo is shared across the
internet thanks to the social network
you built doesn't matter how many times
jesse eisenberg impersonates you on the
big screen you're gonna spend the rest
of your life getting poked because now
everyone knows what you've been trying
to hide you're a nerd if you're still
unsure of whether or not your nerd it's
best to observe one in the wild king
Peter is gonna demonstrate some common
nerd calls I suggest starting with a
simple true cowboy bebop cowboy bebop
and once you've mastered that you can
upgrade to a more advanced calling
response yo did you say for the haptic
rice scene I stayed so long I saw the
real secret scene they're not sure
cleaning the aisles and if you want to
some of the huge flock of nerds
I suggest the mating dance so yes you
are a nerd it's just a matter of when
and how
I'm expert Natasha van block and I'm
Lord watch your King James and your
worst fear has been confirmed the void
resets at midnight so they'll be wiped
from the system what no I am the system
I stayed so long I saw the real secret
seen my mom picking me up from the
theater I stayed so long I saw the real
secret scene a midnight showing of Rocky
Horror a 3:30 p.m. showing of Sam
Mendez's 1917 I stayed so long I saw the
real secret scene and usher cleaning the
aisles
yo yo what's going on issue boy King
baby I'm here at Comedy Central and I'm
gonna be here all week okay so if you're
from my channel you guys support okay
comment below so I can see you also
check all these videos don't forget to
Like comment and subscribe we out here
we gonna be here all week
so you better watch all right support
because it's gonna be amazing great
content amazing content man stop it why
aren't you watching go click go go back
and watch you again just